{
  "shortDescription": "Test your knowledge of Boston NBA champs!",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "How many titles?",
      "answers": ["17", "18", "19"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Larry's last name?",
      "answers": ["Bird", "Magic", "King"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Paul's last name?",
      "answers": ["King", "Pierce", "Bird"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Red?",
      "answers": ["Coach", "Player", "Owner"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Green's first name?",
      "answers": ["Robert", "Gerald", "Bill"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Bill's last name?",
      "answers": ["Jones", "Smith", "Russell"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Jersey color?",
      "answers": ["Blue", "Green", "Red"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "1960s titles?",
      "answers": ["8", "9", "10"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Big 3 era?",
      "answers": ["1980s", "2000s", "2010s"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Current arena?",
      "answers": ["Garden", "Staples", "Arena"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Boston's mascot?",
      "answers": ["Lucky", "Benny", "Rocky"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "1976 Finals MVP?",
      "answers": ["White", "Bird", "Russell"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Team's city?",
      "answers": ["Boston", "LA", "NY"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "First title year?",
      "answers": ["1957", "1967", "1977"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Nickname?",
      "answers": ["C's", "Lakers", "Bulls"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "8 straight titles?",
      "answers": ["1960s", "1970s", "1980s"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Team's founder?",
      "answers": ["Auerbach", "Russell", "Bird"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "K.C.'s last name?",
      "answers": ["Jones", "Smith", "Green"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "NBA titles?",
      "answers": ["17", "16", "15"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Retired number?",
      "answers": ["23", "6", "32"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    }
  ]
}



